livefromspace.com 2009-07-22

# Badpuppy

## Privacy Statement for www.badpuppy.com

Badpuppy Enterprises, Inc has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: www.badpuppy.com. 

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, maintain proper security information for the credit card corporations and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is used to help identify you and your shopping cart. 

Our site uses cookies to keep track of your shopping cart. We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests and for other purposes. 

Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name and email address), financial information (like their checking account or credit card numbers), and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). We use customer contact information from the registration form to send the user information about our company. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Financial information that is collected is used to bill the user for products and services. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor the visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. 

This site contains links to other sites. **www.badpuppy.com** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

Our site uses a request form for customers to request information on products, and services. We collect visitor's contact information (like their email address), financial information (like their account or credit card numbers), and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). Contact information from the order form is used to send orders to our customers. The customer's contact information is used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Financial information that is collected is used to bill the user for products and services. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. 

Our online surveys ask visitors for contact information (like their email address). The customer's contact information is used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. 

We run contests on our site in which we ask visitors for contact information (like their email address) and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). The customer's contact information is used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. 

## Public Forums

This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

## Security

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. We know immediately when a users access to Badpuppy.com has been compromised. Access is immediately terminated thereby protecting the users account. 

## Children's Guidelines

According to the answers that you have chosen, your Web site meets the guidelines of TRUSTe's Children's program. 

  1. NOT collect online contact information
  2. NOT collect personally identifiable offline contact information
  3. NOT distribute to third parties any personally identifiable information
  4. NOT give the ability to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable contact information
  5. NOT entice by the prospect of a special game, prize or other activity, to divulge more information than is needed to participate in the activity

## Choice/Opt-Out

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor.

This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service. 

  1. You can send email to [support@badpuppy.com](mailto:support@badpuppy.com)
  2. You can send mail to the following postal address:  Security - ETrust c/o BEI 414 High Point Drive Cocoa, FL 32926 
  3. You can call the following telephone number: 321.631.9500

## Correct/Update

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided. 

  1. email [support@badpuppy.com](mailto:support@badpuppy.com)
  2. send mail to the following postal address:  Security - ETrust c/o BEI 414 High Point Drive Cocoa, FL 32926 

## Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact William G Pinyon Badpuppy Enterprises, Inc 414 High Point Drive Cocoa, FL 32926 [rivers@badpuppy.com](mailto:rivers@badpuppy.com)
